medplusbeauty.com 2014-02-09

# MedPlus Beauty - Personal Care, Health and Beauty Store Online in India

Our goal at **[www.medplusbeauty.com](http://www.medplusbeauty.com/ "www.medPlusbeauty.com")**  is to make your shopping experience **comfortable** , **safe** , and **convenient**. Protecting your privacy is very important to us. We have accordingly developed this Privacy Policy to protect your personal information and keep it confidential. We endeavour to comply with laws of other countries but cannot and do not warrant that we do. We do everything we reasonably can to protect your rights of privacy on systems and the websites controlled by us, but we are not liable for any unauthorised or unlawful disclosures of your personal and confidential information made by third parties who are not subject to our control, for example advertisers and websites that have links to our website.

######  **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

######  **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

\- **To personalize your experience**  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- **To improve our website**  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- **To improve customer service**  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

\- **To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

\- **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

\- **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

######  **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We use Internet standard encryption technology to scramble your personal data when you transmit it to us. This process is known as SSL (secure sockets layer) and we are constantly updating our technology to provide you with the maximum practicable level of security. To check you are in a secure area of our web site you can look at the bottom right of your browser window and you will see a closed padlock or an unbroken key. This indicates that SSL is enabled and your transaction is secure.

We additionally offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

######  **Safety and Security Tips**

  * When using a public computer or terminal, always log out and close the browser when you complete an online session.
  * Do not tell anyone your password. Do not write your password down anywhere. Remember, anybody who knows your password can access your account or pass your password on to someone else.
  * Create complex passwords. When you create a password, use at least 8 characters - a combination of letters and numbers is best. Do not use your name, email address, or other personal information that can be easily obtained It is also recommended that you change your password frequently.
  * Use different passwords for any other online accounts you have.

###### **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

######  **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

######  **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

######  **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

######  **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

######  **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

######  **1st September, 2011**
